Night falls upon this planet, but day will come again
Time is the one law—in this time are we imprisoned
Time has but one flaw—it is a time which can be rewritten
Oblivion is not reached through sorrow, but rather by turning to strength
Anguish too, and even sorrow, are just as painless anesthesia
A lone light branches in infinitude
As it takes the shape of countless threads
Followers of the world set off toward this earth, under a dreamlike sky
The prayers of the cross undergo betrayal
A clear blasphemy against God, sins which cannot be severed
The temple curtains rise in an ephemeral moment
Then toward past and future doth the wicked depart
A reconstruction most sinful... that none may know
Night falls upon this planet, but day will come again
Time is the one law—in this time are we imprisoned
Time has but one flaw—it is a time which can be rewritten