I connected a dream to the temptation of time;
it pierces through the tempest behind the blue sky.
Why is it that happiness hides itself?
We will be tested by the seed of sorrow.
Not knowing what to do with the kindness passing by,
I shivered in the darkness of the night.
In this endless loop, I realized
what it is that I mustn't lose.
Enduring the pain, I call out to you, looking in your eyes:
our bond was discovered by fate.
In this world, filled with that which can break,
I want to be able to call our encounter "infinite."
Tears twinkle like the flickering stars,
and everything falls in the past, released by light.
Nothing happens by chance,
even this moment is an inevitable miracle.
Those fingertips I touched with love
aren't here anymore, but the spell isn't broken yet.
I'll get ahead of this scattered time,
struggling to reach Heaven's door.
Pass through these encounters, numerous as the stars,
and embrace a new dawn.
If love is a prayer, then offer it without regrets:
I want to keep on protecting your broken smile.
Enduring the pain, I call out to you, looking in your eyes:
our bond was discovered by fate.
In this world, filled with that which can break,
I want to be able to call our encounter "infinite."