Time will come back
Turning upside down
You live in the maze of all your sadness and pain
If you want more games
Look beyond the gate
I believe there is an unlimited beautiful world out there
Come what may, I'll reach there
Although I know it is not easy
An experiment was a failure
The artificer of the universe
Everything is in the hand of God
Who wrote this story I gotta play?
We share the same fate
Do you believe in this fate?
There's nobody else like you who takes my heart away
The place where one road forks endlessly
From the past to the future
An infinite universe
I'll wipe my tears to smile once again
I recognize your face, your voice
This story has just begun
The endless loop world to other side